kaaiot.io 2019-05-22

# Kaa IoT Product Development Platform — Privacy Policy

## KaaIoT Privacy Policy

Effective Date: May 25, 2018

KaaIoT Technologies LLC. (“KaaIoT Technologies”, “Us,” “Our,” or “We”) HAS CREATED THIS PRIVACY POLICY DESCRIBING OUR POLICIES AND PROCEDURES FOR THE COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE OF USER INFORMATION. PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TO LEARN MORE ABOUT OUR PRIVACY POLICY, AND HOW WE TREAT INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM OUR VISITORS AND USERS.

This Privacy Policy is effective to all visitors and users of KaaIoT websites (“Site”) and on which We have incorporated this Privacy Policy, and all products and services offered through Our Site. This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures for collection, use, and disclosure of user information. The terms “You” and “Your” refer to visitors, users, or viewers of the Site.

BY ACCESSING AND USING THE SITE YOU AFFIRM THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THAT YOU AGREE TO THESE TERMS.

### Information We Collect

We may collect Personal Data voluntarily provided by You when You contact Us, sign up for Our newsletter, participate in webinars, create a user account, download materials, participate in promotional activities, download or use Our products, or provide such information through other electronic means. Personal Data We collect may include information such as Your:

  * Name, surname;
  * Email address;
  * Telephone number;
  * Company;
  * Job position.

We may also automatically collect other information that may directly or indirectly identify You for the purpose of ensuring the quality of Our Site, products, and Services, such as Your:

  * Computer’s IP address;
  * Browser information;
  * Cookie information;
  * Domain name;
  * Geographic location;
  * Pages You viewed and the number of times viewed.

We may also collect other information about Your use of the Site using third party tools such as Google Analytics.

_By submitting any Personal Data to Us, You consent and agree that We may collect, use, and disclose such Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and Our Terms of Use, and as permitted or required by law. If You do not agree with these terms, please do not provide any Personal Data to Us. If You refuse or withdraw Your consent, or if You choose not to provide Us with any required Personal Data, We may not be able to provide You with the Services that are offered on Our Site._

### Your Rights

You may at any time withdraw consent or modify Your preferences regarding how We communicate with You in Your Account Settings, by following the “unsubscribe” link located at the bottom of Our marketing and newsletter emails.

If You reside in the EEA, You have additional rights, such as: the right to request access to any Personal Data We hold about You, request that any inaccurate Personal Data is corrected, request an electronic copy of Your Personal Data, or request that Your Personal Data is deleted, provided that Your Personal Data is not required to exercise or defend a legal claim against Us, or for compliance with a legal obligation under the laws of the European Union or a Member State. You may exercise these rights by contacting Us at [privacy@kaaiot.io](mailto:privacy@kaaiot.io). Please note that any communication must be in English.

### How We Use Your Personal Data

We may use Your Personal Data to:

  * Personalize Your experience (Your information helps Us better respond to Your individual needs);
  * Improve Our Site and Services (We continuously strive to improve Our Site offerings based on the information and feedback We receive from You);
  * Improve customer service (Your information helps Us more effectively respond to Your customer service requests, inquiries, and support needs);
  * Contact You by telephone or email regarding products You have purchased or Services You have signed up for;
  * With Your consent, occasionally contact You by telephone or by email to provide You with new product information, technical updates, and information about Our support Services;
  * Respond to You when You send Us an email or otherwise contact Us;
  * Perform marketing surveys to better understand the needs of prospective clients and partners;
  * Provide You with technical support, where required.

### How We Share Your Information

We do not sell Your Personal Data to outside parties, however, there are certain circumstances in which We may share Your Personal Data, including if required by law or by a court order, or if such disclosure is necessary and permitted by law to protect ourselves or third parties. We share Your information only with trusted third parties, such as affiliated companies within Our corporate group and service providers, as necessary for them to perform services on Our behalf, such as:

  * Process credit card payments;
  * Serve advertisements;
  * Provide cloud storage or email services;
  * Conduct surveys;
  * Perform analysis of Our Services and customers demographics;
  * Communicate with You, by email or telephone;
  * Customer relationship management.

These third parties include CRM solution provides, such as Salesforce, email service providers, such as Google, and website analytics providers, such as Google Analytics, which are subject to strict data processing terms and conditions and are prohibited from unauthorized use or transfer of Your Personal Data.

### Transfer of Personal Data to Other Countries

We will not transfer Personal Data originating from the European Economic Area (EEA) to third parties located outside of the EU without ensuring adequate protection under European law. Some of Our service providers may process Your Personal Data outside the EEA. Where transfer of Personal Data is made to a country not recognized by the EU Commission as ensuring an adequate level of protection, We will take appropriate steps, such as enforcing standard contractual clauses recognized by the EU Commission, to safeguard Your Personal Data and to ensure legally enforceable remedies are available. 

### Retention of Personal Data

If You reside or are located in the EEA, We keep Your Personal Data for no longer than necessary for the purposes for which the Personal Data is processed. The length of time We retain Personal Information for depends on the purposes for which We collect and use it or as required to comply with applicable laws and to establish, exercise, or defend Our legal rights.

### Security

We are committed to security and implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of Your Personal Data. We use physical, technical, and administrative security measures to keep Your Personal Data confidential and secure, and will not share it with third parties, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, or unless such disclosure is necessary in special cases.

### User Accounts

Certain features of the Site, Services, or Content may require that You register by providing Personal Data, such as Your email address.

You agree that the information You provide is accurate, and that You are not prohibited by law from registering. Users in the European Union who are under the age of sixteen (16), and users in the United States under the age of thirteen (13), are not permitted to provide Personal Data or create an account with Us. If We believe that a registration has been created by an individual who is under the minimum age in their jurisdiction, all information received by such individual shall be promptly deleted.

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), and do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our Site, products, and Services are all directed to users in the United States who are at least 13 years old or older. 

### Changes to Privacy Policy

KaaIoT Technologies reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, in Our discretion. We will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and any other places We deem appropriate. If We make material changes to this Privacy Policy, We will notify You here, by email, or by means of a notice on Our Site’s home page. Your continued use of this Site following any changes to this Policy shall constitute Your acceptance of the changes and the revised terms.

### Website Links

Our Site may contain links to other websites. While We try to link only to websites that share Our high standards and respect for privacy, please understand that We are not responsible for the content of the privacy practices employed by other websites.

### Who We Are

KaaIoT Technologies, LLC is a Delaware limited liability company, with its principal place of business at 16047 Collins Ave. Suite 2104, North Miami Beach, FL 33160.

### Contact us

If You have any questions, concerns, or complaints about Our Privacy Policy, Our practices, or Our Services, You may contact Us by email at [privacy@kaaiot.io](mailto:privacy@kaaiot.io). Please note that any communication must be in English.
